Our story begins in a land far away, in a time known to none, in a place known to none.
There once was a young king who ruled the kingdom of Heinrogue.
Who goes there!?
It's me.
Forgive my rudeness, your highness.
You're the knight captain?
Yes, Captain Jenatos, sir.
Did you think me an enemy?
Only the spirits of the night visit the ramparts at this hour,
let alone the king himself.
I apologize for startling you then.
You did nothing wrong.
Jenatos, please tell me something.
Why is spring so late to come this year?
It is strange... It's been far more cold than normal.
May is supposed to begin tomorrow.
Right, I suppose it is the end of April.
The fields are still white with frost, keeping the plants from budding.
The world should be bathed in the color of vibrant flowers, but not one is to be seen...
Sometimes that's just how nature is...
Nothing good has happened since my father died and I took the throne.
That's... You're worrying too much, your highness.
Famine. Plague. War. Am I just too weak?
Is the kingdom doomed to suffer at the hands of a novice king in their twenties?
What are you saying, your highness!?
The country needs its king the most when times are tough.
What could I even do?
I'm powerless to help the kingdom.
I wish I had strength.
I wish I had knowledge...
Ravens again... They've been increasing, haven't they?
Probably... since there's been more deaths lately...
Ten... Twenty... Where are they headed?
Probably to the barren mountains.
...you said you desired power, did you not?
Yeah. I suppose I did.
What must a monarch have to turn an ashen country into a prosperous one?
As I've said, the king's abilities affect the kingdom.
That is not all.
Go on...
Every man needs a source of power. A king is no exception.
You mean...
Powerful kings of yore had powerful benefactors.
Benefactors?
I'm sure you know of the stone ruins on top of that barren mountain.
Of course, the temple that once laid there.
When night comes again, head there.
Your wishes will surely be granted.
What do you mean, Jenatos!?
You'll have to find out on your own. Now if you'll excuse me, I need to patrol.
Allow me to read tomorrow's schedule, your highness.
Go ahead.
In the morning, an ambassador from our neighbor wishes to meet with you.
Would you like a private reception room? Or in the public hall?
Either.
Private room, it is. Next, the mayor of Rune Malna wishes to see you.
Ah.
Are you listening, your highness?
I'm listening. What does he want?
It seems to be about the worsening food supplies.
Not like my words will fix anything...
After lunch, you—
That's enough.
But, your highness—
Leave the schedule there. I'll make sure to read it.
Understood. Good night then, your highness.
You too.
Dear.
Marina...
You seem dreadfully tired...
It's nothing.
You should get to bed right away.
There's somewhere I have to go tonight.
At this hour? Where to?
I'll be back before you know it. Please don't wait up for me, okay?
It's an important time to take care of your body, so please rest.
If you insist...
Hello, my lady. Is the king not coming to bed yet?
N-no... Something seems to have come up.
In that case, let's lower your hair and get you ready for bed.
Thanks, Julia.
I'm so jealous of your beautiful long, blonde hair~
Your chestnut-brown hair is lovely too, Julia.
Thanks!
But wow, the king is really cool yet gentle, isn't he?
...I hope Lewis comes back soon.
What's this light?
Good evening! Where you off to at this hour?
And you are?
Fara! And you?
King Lewis.
Ahh! You're a human king!
Hmm, but wasn't the king, uh, Rudolph or something?
That was my great-grandfather.
Oh right, I forget that humans don't live all that long.
Are you a fairy?
Pixie.
Pixie?
Hey, Lewis, this might be rude of me, but you shouldn't go any further this way.
Why not?
It seems a bunch of monsters are gathering on the mountain.
What!?
Well then, I'm off! In a bit of a hurry myself.
What was I in a hurry for again...?
What the...? Why did Jenatos tell me to come to a gathering of ghouls and goblins...?
Ah!
You kept us waiting.
Our special guest has arrived, but he seems to be hiding! Hehehehe...
There! You must be Heinrogue's king, right?
Y-yes.
You're not the first I've seen. You wish for power, do you not?
Who are you?
I'm asking if you wish for power, riches, and wisdom!?
Yes...!
Good...
I shall make you the richest, wisest, and most powerful of kings. Now, stick out your hand.
Ah!
All you must do is accept this ring, and your wishes shall be granted.
-Um—
-Now, put on the ring!
Or what, are you afraid?
No...
Perfect. Now, your dreams will now become your reality.
In return... Once the time is right, your most precious thing will become mine.
!!
Hahahahahaha...
You've just entered a blood pact with me, Gizafeal!
HAHAHAHAHA!
AHHHH!!!
A few months passed since then. As promised, King Lewis's luck turned around,
and the country seemed on the road to recovery.
However...
You called for me?
Ah, minister! I've been waiting. I seek your counsel about our current lands.
Alright...
Look at this map. If we wish to extend the highway to Nautilus, we'll have to cut through the Pixian Forest.
While we're there, why don't we just clear the whole forest and turn it into farmland?
But sir, that's there the pixies and elves live—
What can we do? A prosperous nation needs a powerful economy and military.
We can have all of that with this highway.
But—
How much manpower would this take, minister?
My liege, I'm sure you're very much aware,
but the people are exhausted from repeated war and hardships. Any more would be—
It's for the nation! If it falls, the people fall with it.
But...!
Haven't my policies led to our victory at war and the rapid growth of our economy?
Are you saying I'm wrong?
Your happiness does not equal the people's happiness!
Please think of those who lost loved ones to war, or those struggling under heavy taxes!
Aren't my people just that? MY people?
Your highness! Please refrain from speaking like that!!
-You'll turn the people against—
-That's enough!
It was a waste of time talking to my foolish minister.
-Rethink this.
-Stand down.
My lady, it's time to prepare for the banquet.
Another banquet... Luxurious banquets nearly every night can't possibly be a good thing.
Come on, don't say that.
These beautiful clothes and delicacies are being paid for by the people's taxes!
The king will be upset if you don't show up in your finest.
Lewis has really changed... This jewel he gave me was something plundered from our neighboring country!
I can feel the blood on it...
Please, try not to see only the bad in everything.
Let me open the window so we can relax with some fresh air.
What?
Are you the queen?
Huh? A pixie?
Yup, my name's Fara.
Why are you here?
The forest where we all live is being chopped down. Please, do something!
What? The Pixian Forest?
Yes! Another section was just leveled today!
...I had no idea...
The king's just said progress is going smoothly.
Destroying the forest is "progress"!?
That's not what—
I'll try talking with the king. Though, I don't know if he'll listen...
The lush forests don't belong to just one group!
Even humans will fall to ruin if they keep cutting down the trees! Make sure the king knows that!!
Jenatos.
Lord Gizafeal...
Rejoice, for the fruit has ripened.
W-what do you mean?
You must be tired of standing watch on these cold walls.
Right...
You're the knight captain, yet you're treated like dirt.
Meanwhile, the royal family sleeps warm and cozy in the luxury of the castle.
Yeah...
Was it not the soldiers who won the war?
Are you not frustrated?
A... a little...
They're currently indulging in the finest of liquor.
Don't worry, the people will rally behind you.
Kill King Lewis.
Then become the king yourself!
Ah...
Dear, I wish to ask you about the Pixian Forest.
Ahh, the forest we're building the highway through. With that road built, access to the harbor will be much easier.
Please, don't—
Not just the road either! With all that lumber, we can craft ships and use the cleared land for crops.
Oh, we should build a workshop there too to make weapons, and—
Please, reconsider this plan!
That's the home of the pixies and the elves!
That forest... No, all the forests, mountains, and rivers all belong to me!
Hmm, I wonder if the pixies or the elves could be put to work for the benefit of the country...
That's—
Just leave all the political matters to me, okay?
Just relax and enjoy being adorned in the finest clothes and gems the world has to offer!
I do not enjoy that at all...
Marina...
Your highness! The knight captain has urgent business to report.
What a boorish man, interrupting this gathering. Oh well, let him in.
What's the emergency, Jenatos?
Your highness. Your crown seems to have lost some of its luster.
...what are you talking about?
It must feel good gazing down upon the world from your lofty throne.
Jenatos?
Ash has sullied the shine from your crown.
Let me clean it by taking your life!!
What are you doing!?
Stop! Lower your sword at once, Jenatos!!
I'LL HACK AWAY THE ASH FROM THE CROWN!!!
GUARDS! GUARDS!!!
SEIZE HIM!
LET ME GO! I HAVE TO CLEAR THE ASH!!!
OVERWHELM HIM AND TAKE HIM AWAY!!!
UNHAND ME!!! I'M THE RIGHTFUL KING!!!
REMEMBER, YOU'RE IN THE PALM OF GIZAFEAL'S HAND! HE'LL BE COMING FOR YOU NEXT!!!
Are you hurt, your highness!?
I-I'm fine...
What happened to Jenatos!?
I don't know, but he won't see the light of day again after that.
How dreadful. His wife even has a child on the way...
They'll grow up knowing they had a worthless father.
Who is that Gizafeal that Jenatos mentioned?
It's nothing. Just the vile rubbish of a man lost in his own darkness.
What are you doing sulking in a place like this, dear?
Does what happened with Jenatos still bother you?
That's not it... Say, Marina. What would you say my most precious thing in the world is?
How could I possibly know that better than yourself?
Fair. In that case, what's the most important thing to you?
I have many things. You, my dear. My own life, perhaps.
Maybe it'll be our child when they're born. My parents are precious to me too.
I see. All things you can't purchase with wealth, huh.
Of course. You couldn't obtain any of those things with power alone, perhaps not even with wisdom.
What is it, dear?
Marina. I'm... thinking of traveling to Hermit's Island.
Hermit's Island? What for?
They say a skilled diviner lives there. I wish to seek his advice.
Well, he should live inside that cave over there, but—
Got it. I'll be heading there alone. You can return to the ship, minister.
Alright... Be careful.
Bats!?
I've been waiting for you.
You wished to hear of your future self, did you not?
You knew I was coming?
The holy mirror here always reflects what it needs to.
Is it true you can read the future?
Do you wish to find out? But please remember; the future may not hold the happiness you seek.
All people will die one day. That won't phase me.
I speak of the method of your death, not the death itself.
I fear nothing. Let me hear it.
Then, give me your hand. ...oh my.
What?
You bear a burdensome ring. It would best be parted with.
I... can't remove it. It's like it has become one with my flesh.
I see.
Do you know what this ring is?
No, I... I'm making too much of it.
Now, place your hands upon the mirror's pedestal.
-Like this?
-Yes.
Now, the time spirits will bubble forth from the mirror's depths.
What do you see?
I see treasure. The king and the queen. And...
And?
A young child, just born.
Are they a boy? A girl?
I can't see yet. I see them crawling around. Ah, they're a healthy boy!
I see, a boy!
He grows up into a fine lad, no, a splendid man. ...oh no.
W-what?
He...
That's it. The mirror has clouded over.
What happened? What happens to me in the end!?
...you would be better off not knowing.
Do I die of disease? In battle?
Much worse...
I grow tired of this! Just tell me already!!
You fall to the ground... at the hands of your own son.
My son... kills me? Are you sure?
I'm afraid so.
This mirror must be spitting lies!
It is possible, I suppose. Though it has never lied before now.
Is there no changing it? My destiny?
I... do not know of such a way.
How could this be...?
With a heavy heart, the king returned to Heinrogue.
The terrible prophecy from the diviner repeated in his head over and over.
You fall to the ground... at the hands of your own son.
What troubles you, my lord?
It's nothing.
Did you learn anything from the diviner?
Nothing important.
Whatever you heard, don't let it bother you.
I know...
Do you think he'll be back tonight, Julia?
I'm sure he will be. We received early word from a messenger about his imminent arrival.
Thank goodness... Oh!
What's wrong?
The baby kicked!
Let me see... Oh, there it is! It really won't be much longer now!
Oh, I'm so excited! Will it be a boy? Or a girl?
I can't wait! I'm sure the king will be excited as well!
Definitely! Ahh, I don't want to wait any longer!
The king has arrived!
See, he's here!
Julia, what do you make of those two stars near the horizon?
Hmm... I can't say I've seen those stars before.
It's like they're twins nestling close to each other.
They are twin stars, after all, my lady.
Marina!
Dear!
I'm home.
Welcome home, your highness.
Thanks and good work, Julia.
How were your travels?
Peaceful and uneventful, couldn't have been better.
That's wonderful! So your task at Hermit's Island is finished?
Hmm? A-ahh...
I'll have to hear all about it later.
No, it really wasn't worth talking about. It was a waste of effort, going that far.
That's too bad...
How are you feeling, Marina?
Oh, very well!
Your highness, the child inside of her kicked just a minute ago!
I-I see.
They're a very lively child. If it's a boy, he'll become a strong—
Sorry, I wish to sleep early tonight. Has the bed been prepared?
Yes...
Dear...
Not long after, the queen gave birth to a healthy boy.
Announcing the crown prince!!
Mysteriously, another child was born at the same hour in a house close to the castle.
I've brought dinner, my lady.
I don't have an appetite.
You need to eat something! We'll get you back to health soon to match the lively child you made.
Mhmm. At this rate, however, I'll have to miss out on the naming ceremony.
I see. Oh, I heard an interesting rumor recently.
Another child was born at the same time as the crown prince. Any guesses as to whom?
Who could it be...?
It was Jenatos' child.
Jenatos'?
It's a girl they named Sarina.
Sarina... It must be hard on the mother raising her alone after what her father did...
Yes. It sounds like they're worried about how to raise Sarina alone.
I'd imagine...
Do you think the king might be convinced to pardon him?
Not likely. Insurrection is a terrible crime.
I suppose it is...
Julia, would you mind opening the window? I'd love some fresh air.
Of course.
Ah, fall has clearly arrived. Another week, and the leaves will start falling.
Mhmm. Oh, those twin stars seem to have disappeared.
They were so bright even. It's almost as if the two stars themselves fell down and became your child and Sarina.
It seems like that... It really does...
This child is meant to kill me?
That's just...
If I just twist his neck... he'd die right here.
If I simply drop him from this window...
...would my fate change?
There, there. Forgive me. This will all be over soon.
What are you doing, king!? Stop it! Stop it!!
When did a pixie get here!?
My name's Fara, remember it this time!
Don't get in my way!
What were you doing with the child? You weren't going to throw him out the window, were you!?
N-no...
I don't know what's going on, but it's never okay to raise your hand against a defenseless child!
And isn't this your kid? You're not having an affair with your wife, are you?
Quiet you. How could you say that!?
Haha, sorry, sorry~ Let's just take a step back, okay?
This child will one day—
What a healthy boy! He'll be quite the rascal when he's older.
What did I come here for again... Oh right! I came here to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
The forest we live in is gone now. The pixies and the elves have all left you.
Many went to neighboring countries, others underground. I'm about to leave myself.
You won't be back?
Who knows? But king, try not to make any more mistakes, okay? For both the country and yourself.
And also, try to remember.
Remember what?
Drawing water with a clean bucket leaves the well clean, but a filthy bucket will poison the well forever. Bye now!
Ah...
Your highness?
Ah, Julia.
The minister wishes to go over tomorrow's naming ceremony with you.
Ah, got it...
Aww, aren't you glad your father held you up, you little prince~
He's in quite the good mood, isn't he?
He must love his father.
Your highness, I'll—
He really does look more and more like you by the day~ Maybe he'll grow larger and gaze down upon you!
A-ah...
I'm looking forward to the ceremony tomorrow, your highness.
What kind of a name do you think the Six Gods will bestow upon him?
Who knows.
He was born under the dragon, so I'm sure the Dragon God's disciple will give him a fine name.
Your highness! There you are!
Minister?
I'm being dragged around left and right!
I'm being asked about seating for tomorrow, and now the guests are starting to quarrel with each other! I can't keep up!
I got it, I'll be there shortly.
Well then, how does this sound for the seating of the visiting countries?
Good, no problems here.
Next for the non-humans guests. I'm not sure why, but there's been no response from the elves or the pixies.
They refused the invitation?
No... They seem to have disappeared.
Pay it no mind. It's no great loss.
But the ceremony where the elves and pixies of the kingdom come here has meaning and—
How can we invite who is not there?
On another note, there are rumors of goblins and hobgoblins growing in numbers throughout the kingdom.
We'll pick that topic up another time. Continue.
The disciples of the Six Gods have accepted the invites.
That is to say, the Ocean God, the Mountain God, the Hero God, the Fertility Goddess, the Spirit God, and the Dragon God.
I see.
With them here, I'm sure the naming ceremony will go smoothly.
Then there's no problem, right?
One more thing: as the royal family, you may decide if you wish to extend an invite to the Seventh God.
Seventh God?
The one who rules the Underworld, Gizafeal.
What's wrong, your highness?
Gizafeal is the one who rules over death?
That is correct.
He's... There's no need to invite someone like that to the naming ceremony.
Understood.
Have any of my ancestors ever invited him in the past?
Nothing I've seen in our records going back several hundred years, but in older times—
Why!?
Gizafeal, while ruling over the dead, also rules over pleasure and fortune.
I don't understand! How can he rule such opposites!?
I've been told that those blessed by him with fortune and pleasure must pay the price while they're still of this world.
What...!?
Are you the leader of the goblins?
What's it to you?
I'm King Lewis.
I beg for your forgiveness, your highness! What brings you to this place where the sun doesn't shine?
I request a favor.
We'd do anything for a king! Just, there's always—
A price, I know. Here.
If that's not enough, I'll bring more.
You must have something mighty important you need done! Hahaha!
I need to you kidnap a baby... and kill them.
Before it's too late.
Ambassador of the Hero God!
Ambassador of the Spirit God!
Ambassador of the Dragon God!
Ambassador of the Ocean God!
All the God's disciples seem to be arriving now.
You could be seeing the ceremony in person, you know...
There's no need to worry about me...
Are you okay, my lady!?
I'm sorry. Julia... Do you think I'll be able to see my child's first birthday...?
What are you saying? Of course you will! You'll see him grow into a fine adult and even more beyond that.
I... would love that...
Right about now, the ambassadors should be presenting their gifts.
May the prince grow into a man beautiful in both body and heart.
May the prince grow into a valiant hero who won't give up in the face of any hardship.
May the prince grow into a wise man with both deep knowledge and insight.
What's going on!?
What, did you forget to invite me?
Ahh!
Not only did you fail to invite me, but you thought you could receive my kindness without paying the price.
Halt!
You won't lay a finger on him!
Hmm. I'm not here for the child. I'm here to collect on the king's debt.
W-what do you mean—
Don't play me for a fool! What was mine still resides on your finger.
Is this true, your highness!?
You underestimated me, boy. You made a promise, so now I'm here.
For the sin of trying to dishonor Gizafeal, this country will once again fall into misfortune!
Oh no!
AHH! AHHH!!!
And now, I will claim your most precious possession.
I've watched you closely to the very end, but I've decided.
I'll be taking "you" yourself!
HELP ME!!!
YOUR HIGHNESS!!!
HELP ME!!! AHHH!!!!!
HAHAHAHA!!!
You shall be mine for all eternity!!
-ABOVE! ABOVE! PROTECT HIS HIGHNESS AT ALL COSTS!!!
-YES, SIR!
Minister, please!
What!?
What has fallen into Gizafeal's hands is forever lost. But, we still have the gift from my protector, the Dragon God.
Which is?
It'll weaken Gizafeal's curse, if just a bit.
The prince will grow up and become the dawn upon this kingdom fallen to twilight.
Here and now, the Dragon God bestows upon the prince the name "Kai."
The king...!
They're searching the castle for him now!
How could this be...?
But, at least the prince is safe and was given the name Kai.
Kai...
Look, he's even got a pendant from the Dragon God as proof of the naming ceremony.
What was that sound?
I'm not sure...
There, that's the child! Take him away!
Stop it!
OUTTA THE WAY!
Julia!
HURRY IT UP!
Please stop! What are you doing with him!?
Kill him, of course! Hahaha!
Please, stop! Give Kai back to me! KAI!!!
Before long, the queen fell into despair after losing both her husband and child, and soon took her last breath.
Both the king and the prince have not been seen since.
Due to Gizafeal's curse, the country fell to waste. One by one, the people abandoned the castle as it fell to ruin.
Then, 17 years came and went.
Alright, I'm off, mom!
Are you really going off on a journey, Sarina?
Yeah. I'm off to find my own happiness.
Remember, don't tell anyone about your father. Especially any noblemen!
I know, I know. I hate those stuffy people, so I don't plan on talking to any either way.
Oh look, those two twin stars are back on the dawn's horizon again!
Back again?
They appeared once before on the day you were born.
Hmm. It must be a good sign then. Well, I'm off, mom!
Stay safe, Sarina.
I'll come back for sure, then we can live an easier life.
Hmm~ Should I take a slow journey this year, or laze around the forest some more? I can't decide~
Oh, I should see how the Pixian Forest is doing! Maybe not, I'm sure it's still in terrible shape... No, I should see it anyway!
Hey, Kai? Are we going to be stuck here mining until the day we die?
Don't lose hope, Michelia! I'm sure one day, we'll have our freedom.
How far away will that day be...?
I've actually been thinking of how to get away. I'll make sure we all escape from this slave camp, Michelia.
Really!?
Of course. And, I really want to know about my parents and homeland.
Kai, look! Something's glowing!
Woah, what is that?
I've never seen anything like this...
It gives me the creeps... We should throw it away.
Let's not. This feels like it could be the harbinger for what's to come.
The curtain falls on one story, just as it rises on a new tale.
A tale of young warriors on a boundless adventure.
A new page now turns in the story of Ancient Roman.
Drama cast:
Lewis Orpheus and Kai Orpheus: Naozumi Takahashi (高橋 直純)
Marina Orpheus and Michelia Almayer: Manami Nakayama (中山 真奈美)
Maid Julia, Sarina Jenatos: Saki Nakajima (中島 沙樹)
Fara: Mariko Morimoto (森本 まり子)
Minister: Tetsuo Sakaguchi (坂口 哲夫)
Blore Jenatos, Guards, and Hero God Ambassador: Tomohisa Asō (松丸 卓也)
Gizafeal: Ryūzaburō Ōtomo (大友 龍三郎)
Hermit, Goblin, and Dragon God Ambassador: Shōgo Sakamoto (not that one)
Spirit God Ambassador: Tomoko Fujino (藤野 とも子)
Goddess Ambassador: Kanako Okada (岡田 加奈子)
Narration and Sarina's Mother: Ikuko Tatsu (達 依久子)
Thank you for listening!
(TL Note: Never ask me for anything ever again.)